noxxic.com 2017-06-10

# Privacy Policy - Noxxic

Information is collected and used in various ways that will help Noxxic.com better serve its visitors. 

Information is collected while browsing through our website. This information is collected to help run our site more efficiently, to gather broad demographic information, to monitor the level of activity on our site, and to evaluate the effectiveness of advertising and promotion. 

If you contact us, we may keep a record of your correspondence or comments, including any information therein. We use this information to help us provide better service. 

A "cookie" is a small data file that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system. We use cookies to better serve you when you return to our site. Some of our web pages may send cookies when you visit our site, make purchases, respond to online surveys or promotions, participate in a contest, or request information. Accepting the cookies used on our site enables our web server to identify your system by reading the cookie that has been stored on your system, but our web server cannot identify you unless you enter your Personal Information. Cookies that are placed when visiting our site cannot be used to obtain your Personal Information at another site. The information collected online permits us to analyze traffic patterns on our site. This can enable us over time to provide users with a better experience on our site by improving the content and making it easier to use. Depending on the browser used, you can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it, and you can also set your browser to turn off cookies. However, if you do so, some areas of this site may not function properly, or you will be required to re-enter your Personal Information to use an area of this site. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. to learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://networkadvertising.org. 

If you are under the age of 18, please make sure that you provide your Personal Information only after obtaining your parental consent. 

While Noxxic.com does not guarantee that unauthorized access will never occur, Noxxic.com does take care in maintaining the security of your Personal Information and in preventing unauthorized access to it. 

Parts of our site contain links to our subsidiaries, affiliates and third-party websites for your convenience and information. If you use these links, you will leave Noxxic.com website. When you access these other sites, even ones that may contain the Noxxic.com mark, please understand that we do not control the content and are not responsible for the privacy practices of that website. We suggest that you carefully review the privacy policies of each website you visit. This Online Privacy Statement does not cover the information practices of those websites linked to our site. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit Personal Information. 

Noxxic.com reserves the right to change this Online Privacy Statement at any time. Any such changes will be posted in this Privacy Statement. 

Noxxic.com will protect your Personal Information in accordance with the laws of the United States.
